universitytickets.com 2002-08-02

# UniversityTickets.com: Privacy Statement

### Privacy Statement for UniversityTickets.com

UniversityTickets.com, Inc. has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: UniversityTickets.com. 

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. 

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name and email address), unique identifiers (like their social security number), financial information (like their account or credit card numbers), and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). We use customer contact information from the registration form to send the user information about our company. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Financial information that is collected is used to bill the user for products and services. Unique identifiers (such as social security numbers) are collected to verify the user's identity and for use as account numbers in our record system. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data for other purposes. We use this data to tailor the visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. 

Our site uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect visitor's contact information (like their email address), unique identifiers (like their social security number), and financial information (like their account or credit card numbers). Contact information from the order form is used to send orders, information about our company, and promotional material from some of our partners to our customers. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Financial information that is collected is used to bill the user for products and services. Unique identifiers (such as social security numbers) are collected from Web site visitors to verify the user's identity and for use as account numbers in our record system. 

Our online surveys ask visitors for contact information (like their email address), unique identifiers (like their social security number), and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). We use contact data from our surveys to send the user information about our company. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Unique identifiers (such as social security numbers) are collected from Web site visitors to verify the user's identity and for use as account numbers in our record system. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis. 

We run contests on our site in which we ask visitors for contact information (like their email address), unique identifiers (like their social security number), and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). We use contact data from our contests to send users information about our company. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Unique identifiers (like social security numbers) are collected from Web site visitors to verify the user's identity and for use as account numbers in our record system. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. 

### Security

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. (*Please elaborate on the security measures that you have in place.) 

### Children's Guidelines

According to the answers that you have chosen, your Web site meets the guidelines of TRUSTe's Children's program. 

  1. NOT collect online contact information without prior parental consent or parental notification, which will include an opportunity for the parent to prevent use of the information and participation in the activity. Without prior parental consent, online information will only be used to respond directly to the child's request and will not be used for other purposes without prior parental consent 
  2. NOT collect personally identifiable offline contact information without prior parental consent 
  3. NOT distribute to third parties any personally identifiable information with out prior parental consent 
  4. NOT give the ability to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable contact information without prior parental consent 
  5. NOT entice by the prospect of a special game, prize or other activity, to divulge more information than is needed to participate in the activity

### Choice/Opt-Out

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor. 

This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. 

  1. You can send email to [privacy@universitytickets.com](mailto:privacy@universitytickets.com)

### Correct/Update

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. 

  1. email [privacy@universitytickets.com](mailto:privacy@universitytickets.com)

### Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can send corrections to the address below: 

  1. email [privacy@universitytickets.com](mailto:privacy@universitytickets.com)
